<?xml version="1.0"?>
	<study>
		<name>Posner Test</name>
		
		<api_name>posner_test</api_name>
		
		<description>Posner Test is a test of your attention.</description>
		
		<consent>This experiment will not put you in any danger.
		Pinky Promise?</consent>
		
		<instructions>General Instruction: You will fixate on the center point on the screen.
		Click left if the left point blinks. Click right if the right
		point blinks. More detailed instructions will be provided later.</instructions>
		
		<eligibility>This test is specialized toward people with
		lesions in the cerebellum. You must be screened by the doctor
		first.</eligibility>
		
		<reward>$12/hr and free imaging of your brain.</reward>
	
		<start_date>2015-09-10</start_date>
		
		<end_date>2015-09-30</end_date>
	
		<!-- All users who should be able to administer the study. Investigators
		CANNOT be participants! -->
		<investigators>
			<user name="kante"/>
			<user name="nalatie"/>
		</investigators>
	
		<!-- 
			List the directories of all stages in your study here (order is not 
			important in this section)
		-->
		<stages>
			<stage number="1">
				<name>EGG Installation</name>
				<description>At this tage, an assistant will install EGG hat on your head.</description>
				<instructions>Follow the instructions provided by the assistant.</instructions>
				<url></url>
			</stage>
			<stage number="2">
				<name>Posner Task I</name>
				<description>Perform the Posner Task I</description>
				<instructions>There are three points on the screen. Focus your eye on the central point.
				Put your hand on your mouse. Click either of the buttons on the mouse to start the test.
				The left and right points will blink arbritarily. Click left when the left point blinks
				and click right when the right point blinks. Occassionally, other objects may appear
				on the screen, do not be alaramed.</instructions>
				<url>posner_1.html</url>
			</stage>
			<stage number="3">
				<name>Posner Task II</name>
				<description>Perform the Posner Task II</description>
				<instructions>The instruction is the same with the first one. There are three points on 
				the screen. Focus your eye on the central point. Put your hand on your mouse. Click 
				either of the buttons on the mouse to start the test. The left and right points will blink 
				arbritarily. Click left when the left point blinks and click right when the right point 
				blinks. Occassionally, other objects may appear on the screen, do not be alaramed.
				</instructions>
				<url>posner_2.html</url>
			</stage>
			
		</stages>
	
	
		<!-- One entry for each distinct group in the study -->
		<groups>
			<group>
				<name>Cerebellar Agenesis</name>
				<users>
					<user name="charlesb"/>
				</users>
				<stage_orders>
					<order>1</order>
					<order>2</order>
					<order>3</order>
				</stage_orders>
			</group>
			
			<group>
				<name>Cerebellar Stroke</name>
				<users>
					<user name="adal"/>
					<user name="alant"/>
					<user name="allenn"/>
				</users>
				<stage_orders>
					<order>1</order>
					<order>2</order>
					<order>3</order>
				</stage_orders>
			</group>
		</groups>

	</study>